– The creature smashes against the police car while Lee is speaking to Officer Ronnie.
– A creature lands on a car in front of Evelyn and her kids.
– As Evelyn blindly drives in reverse, a creature climbs out of a smashed tour bus windshield.
– The creature leaps towards Officer Ronnie and slams into the police car.
– Evelyn steps on a trip wire which drops a large rope full of glass bottles.
– Marcus steps on a bear trap alerting the aliens to the family’s location.
– Emmett grabs Evelyn as she enters the refinery to silence her as an alien crawls down the wall behind her.
– Reagan is startled by a pack of birds hiding in the train.
– The body of a dead person falls against Reagan as she releases the first aid box from the train’s restroom.
– Reagan doesn’t hear the creature board the train after she falls backward.
– Emmett is startled by something as he attempts to unmoor the boat.
– An unknown girl startles Emmett.
– Marcus parts the curtain and discovers Emmett’s wife’s corpse.
– A creature leaps onto the convertible and rips open the soft top.
– A creature leaps onto the convertible AGAIN!
– A creature grabs a man and drags him out from under a garage door.
– A creature rips off the door.
– A creature rips the furnace door open as Evelyn tries to close and lock it.